const fastestFingerData =
    [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Arrange this Safety PPE according to their usage  from Head to Toe.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Safety Shoes"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Safety Goggles"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Hand gloves"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Safety Helmet"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dbca"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Arrange this Risk order from High to Low Risk category.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. White"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Turquoise"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Purple"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Blue"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "cdba"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Arrange this Injury category  form High to Low severity.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. LWC"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. FAC"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. RWC"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. MTC"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "acdb"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Arrange this PPE from its service temp. in order to from High to Low.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Boiler Suit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Chemical protective suit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Hot splash suit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Aluminised Suit"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dcba"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Arrange this Safety PPE according to their usage  from Toe  to Head",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Hand gloves"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Safety Goggles"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Safety Shoes"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Safety Helmet"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "cabd"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Arrange this hierarchy of controls of HITRA from Higher protection  to Lower protection.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. PPEs "
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Elimination"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Substitution"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Engineering Control"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "bcda"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Arrange the correct sequence of fire extinguisher operation for extinguish fire.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Sweep"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Aim"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Squeeze"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Pull"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dbca"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Arrange this sequential steps of basic HITRA Process",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Control measures"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Monitoring"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Identify the hazards"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. List out Task/ Sub tasks"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dcab"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Arrange the sequential order before entering in confined space",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Provision of stand by person"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Confined space entry"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Obtained work permit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Gas Monitoring"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dcab"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Arrange the sequential order for hot work jobs",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Hot work"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Issued permit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. LEL Checking "
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Booth Preparation"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dcba"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Arrange the sequential order before starting pump maintenance work.",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Try Test"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Start Maintenance Job"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Issued permit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. LOTO"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "dcab"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "Arrange in sequential order for the type of isolation with respect to reliability for man entry in confined space job. (1 as more reliable)",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Single valve isolation.  "
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Spool dismantle and to provide rated end blind "
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Double block and bleed"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Provide slip blind or reversing of spectacle blind. "
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "bdca"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Arrange following Hazardous Area Classification in order of It's  Flammable Gases concentration from Higher to Lower",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Zone 2"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Safe"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Zone 0"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Zone 1"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "cdab"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Arrange Electrical Voltage level based on It's Electrical Shock Potential - Lower to Higher",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. 230 V"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. 415 V"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. 230 KV"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. 11 KV"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "abdc"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Arrange following category of  permit approver based on their authority  - Higher to Lower",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Approver I"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Approver III"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Approver II"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Field Executive"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "bcad"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "Arrange Process Safety Incident category based on it' s Risk Potential - Higher to Lower",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Tier III"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Tier I"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. Tier II"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. Tier IV"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "bcad"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "Arrange following HSEF Events based on their occurrence in the year from January to December",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "text": "A. Environment Day"
                },
                {
                    "text": "B. Annual Safety Campaign"
                },
                {
                    "text": "C. HTM Awareness Week"
                },
                {
                    "text": "D. National Fire Service Day"
                }
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "bdac"
        }
    ];

export { fastestFingerData};

